Finding Aid for the David Mcdowell Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- James Agee Trust. Copyright and Royalty Agreements (Box 4)
  - Houghton Mifflin Company and the James Agee Trust 20 December 1966 - The Poems of James Agee, edited by Robert Fitzgerald
  - Houghton Mifflin Company and the James Agee Trust 21 November 1967 - James Agee Poetry and James Agee Prose, both edited by Robert Fitzgerald
  - Yale University Press and James Agee 14 September 1934 - "Permit Me Voyage"
- Agee Library and James Agee Trust. Miscellanea (Box 4)
- Clippings (Box 5)
- Excerpts (Box 5)
- Insurance Records (Box 5)
- Magazines (Box 5)
- Manuscripts (Box 5)
- Photographs (Box 5)
- Programs (Box 5)
- Publicity Statements (Box 5)
- Rough Drafts and Notes (Box 5)
- Test (Box 5)